<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Stories By RedEagle3</title>
    <link href="https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages" />
    <updated>2020-11-07T10:03:19+11:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>RedEagle3</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Night of the Dead</title>
        <author>
            <name>RedEagle3</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/night-of-the-dead/"/>
        <id>https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/night-of-the-dead/</id>
            <category term="Short Stories"/>
            <category term="Halloween Vault 3D Entries 2020"/>

        <updated>2020-11-07T10:03:19+11:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/media/posts/14/NightOfTheDead.png" alt="" />
                    <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Carrie walked with Maxon and the two of them were doing what every other ten-year-old would be doing. They were out trick or treating. Carrying their plastic jack-o'-lanterns they walked in-sync across the pavement and went to the next house.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The previous lady had been really nice and had given both of them more than a few big chunks of chocolate. Although they weren’t so successful on their second attempt, a bunch of teenage kids opened the door. Behind them, both Carrie and Maxon could see the big pile of sweets that would even make a dentist drool.</span></p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/media/posts/14/NightOfTheDead.png" alt="" />
                <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Carrie walked with Maxon and the two of them were doing what every other ten-year-old would be doing. They were out trick or treating. Carrying their plastic jack-o'-lanterns they walked in-sync across the pavement and went to the next house.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The previous lady had been really nice and had given both of them more than a few big chunks of chocolate. Although they weren’t so successful on their second attempt, a bunch of teenage kids opened the door. Behind them, both Carrie and Maxon could see the big pile of sweets that would even make a dentist drool.</span></p>

<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Whatcha doin’ here kiddies?” One of the guys asked he had a blue headband which pressed tight against his bulging forehead. Beside him, there were two more boys who looked like they had recently inhaled a submarine each and two more girls who were in scary costumes with faces caked with makeup.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Trick or treating,” Carrie said not even flinching at the older kids who so obviously wanted them gone.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“We don’t have any candy, kiddie,” blue headband asked and it immediately became clear why he had a bulging forehead. Behind the group huddled in front of the door there was an extremely large pile of snacks, chocolates, candy and lollies.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“You greedy pig! You’re supposed to share the goodies not hog it!” Carrie screamed in his face.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“What are you going to do about it kiddie?” He said stepping forward, all in their faces. At that exact moment, both Carrie and Maxson knew they were toast that a child would have with butter. Maxon didn’t even have time to scream </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Run! </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">before those kids started chasing them.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Even though they were disadvantaged in their size, speed, stamina and probably every other physical trait they stilled held a chance, these kids wouldn’t know what hit them because they had a strategy, all those years of playing tips wouldn’t fail them now.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Use plan Alpha, if that failed Beta!” Maxon yelled as they ran past families and more than a few groups of children to stir clear of those ogres.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">They ran till the end of the street and split, that’ll buy them a few seconds. Then after losing the tails they would meet up at a different location depending on the time of the day.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Maxon kept running, even after the sound of feet colliding with the pavement and the heavy breathing stopped. He still ran. Glancing at his watch, 1:17 am. He pivoted on this right foot and ran to Almond Park.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When he reached there he watched in horror as Carrie was dragged off by a see-through the figure that looked vaguely humanoid.</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Oh hell no, </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">he thought. </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">That’s not possible. Ghosts don’t exist.</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That was when Carrie had spotted him and screamed for his help. He backed up as the figure turned with Carrie still in its grasp. Its eyes were endless pits of darkness and as it opened its mouth a blood churning scream tore over the town.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Carrie matched its vocals by producing her own scream of equal glory. That was when he realised that he might never see her again.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gathering together all his valour he charged forward but just as he reached them, Carrie and the devil’s minion walked through the portal and he watched as his closest friend was dragged into a pool of shadows screaming bloody murder.</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Twisted Halloween</title>
        <author>
            <name>RedEagle3</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/twisted-halloween/"/>
        <id>https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/twisted-halloween/</id>
            <category term="Short Stories"/>
            <category term="Halloween Vault 3D Entries 2020"/>

        <updated>2020-11-07T10:02:26+11:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/media/posts/13/163ec3706bb256cd663743788629.png" alt="Profile Prompt: Twisted Halloween" />
                    <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gothel was walking back from the mall when she saw other children her age heading toward the public library. They were the same set of people, every week, every time she walked to get the groceries. And just like every time she debated, would she go over? Would she say hi? No, just like every time she continued walking pretending to pay no attention to the group of girls and boys from her school.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">She picked up her pace, she was behind schedule. If she wasn’t home by five, her mother would get worried. She unlocked the door, went in and locked it before calling her mother.</span></p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/media/posts/13/163ec3706bb256cd663743788629.png" alt="Profile Prompt: Twisted Halloween" />
                <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Gothel was walking back from the mall when she saw other children her age heading toward the public library. They were the same set of people, every week, every time she walked to get the groceries. And just like every time she debated, would she go over? Would she say hi? No, just like every time she continued walking pretending to pay no attention to the group of girls and boys from her school.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">She picked up her pace, she was behind schedule. If she wasn’t home by five, her mother would get worried. She unlocked the door, went in and locked it before calling her mother.</span></p>

<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“I’m home, mhm, yes I got the bread. Anything else? Sure.” She ended the landline and slowly unloaded the groceries.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A few hours passed as she read books and studied for her math test, taking note of the time she sprang up and started on her chores, she mopped and vacuumed and did the dishes and baked. After a few cakes or two, she picked up her tablet and began sketching.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For hours she sat there, her stylus moving over the screen in an almost hypnotic pattern. When she finished her masterpiece she screenshotted it and uploaded it to the internet to be viewed by millions of people across the world. This was her only way of communicating other than that occasional conversation at school.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Uploading art was her thing, and the more she did it the more she liked it. She felt connected to others and it also made her feel a bit like a rebel. Like she was secretly leading a secret life. But if she put it that way it did sound so special anymore. Her mother worked at this fashion company and was rarely not in contact with her. She was usually overseas at places organising events. She walked over to the balcony and opened it.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">She was looking down as the evening breeze moved through her hair making it fly out behind her in all directions. There were more than five hundred feet below her and there was this sense of déjà vu. Stretching she grabbed her brush and got ready to brush down her curly, raven, black hair.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">She brushed and brushed and brushed some more. Still stuck in the same place, wondering and wondering when her life would begin.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Honey!” A voice shouted from outside, outside her world.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Comming!” She strode to the door the furniture snagging on some of her hair. She bundling up her dark hair and opened the door for her mother.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A few moments later a lady in light purple robe entered the room and lowered her hood. A mane of blond locks tumbled out and over her shoulders like water would in a waterfall.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Hello honey, how was school?” Rapunzel asked her in that posh accent.</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Ambassadors UK&#x27;s The Harbinger</title>
        <author>
            <name>RedEagle3</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/ambassadors-uks-the-harbinger/"/>
        <id>https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/ambassadors-uks-the-harbinger/</id>
            <category term="Short Stories"/>
            <category term="Halloween Vault 3D Entries 2020"/>

        <updated>2020-11-07T10:02:08+11:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/media/posts/12/163e7467bcaa8cb0423950609030.png" alt="Prompt: Corpse Candles" />
                    <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Annie, do you mind putting out the recycling and dry the clothes?”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Sure mother, I’ll be back.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Annie packed up her stuff and strode over to the family’s recycling bin that had been overflowing for weeks. Now </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">that </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">is what happens when someone doesn’t do their share of work, she thought to herself as she grabbed both of the handles and carefully lifted it up, trying not to drop anything. The attempt was in vain as cardboard boxes and pieces of crumpled paper cascaded onto the floor. Sighing, she stepped over the pile that had formed on the ground and walked to the front door.</span></p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/media/posts/12/163e7467bcaa8cb0423950609030.png" alt="Prompt: Corpse Candles" />
                <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Annie, do you mind putting out the recycling and dry the clothes?”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Sure mother, I’ll be back.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Annie packed up her stuff and strode over to the family’s recycling bin that had been overflowing for weeks. Now </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">that </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">is what happens when someone doesn’t do their share of work, she thought to herself as she grabbed both of the handles and carefully lifted it up, trying not to drop anything. The attempt was in vain as cardboard boxes and pieces of crumpled paper cascaded onto the floor. Sighing, she stepped over the pile that had formed on the ground and walked to the front door.</span></p>

<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Ma! Benjamin! There’s a bit of paper on the floor! I’ll pick it up later!” Annie told the current residents of the house, their father went to get milk five years ago and to this day they still didn’t receive that dam milk carton.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After the recycling was done she went to the laundry room and gathered up all the clothes into a basket and grabbed some pegs. This time she walked into the back yard and walked over to the drying line near the old shed that hadn’t been used in a few years and an out-of-stock dunny.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It was then that it happened like it did every Halloween.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">All around her fireflies started to appear, illuminating the evening. Handy, she thought. Do you know what fireflies are the best at doing? Lightin’ up the area. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Apparently, someone didn’t agree. The neighbours in their backyard mumbled under their breath and wobbled back inside their house. Annie didn’t find their reactions strange, every year on Halloween these fireflies would surround her, whether she was inside, outside or on the way inside. They were always there. And as if on cue the neighbours would go inside and lock all their doors tight.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The neighbours were an old couple from the UK, they use to always came over during New Years and sometimes even Christmas but ever since those fireflies appeared they kept their distance. At first, they warned mother that it was an omen of death but as the fireflies came each year, she waved the warnings away as superstition.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“But they’re jack o’lanters, corpse candles, the dead man’s candles!” The old lady would warn as if the words would mean something to us.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Don’t be silly, those are just fairytales.” Mother said.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Blimey, whatever you say. They’re watching. You better watch out. We warned you. Don’t say we didn’t.” The old man said, looking at me with his one dark brown eye and his other milky white eye, almost as if he could see with two of them.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After they had left that day, so many years ago she couldn’t sleep as the fireflies came and surrounded her. She tossed and turned, their voices in her ears, she jumped at every small sound, wondering if a demon would jump out and murder her right there on the spot. But the night came and went, she was alive and over the next few years she agreed with her mother, it was just a scary Halloween story based on raw superstition.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It was an odd thing, those fireflies. They would come and go, come and go, like the tide. She always dismissed them as fireflies but boy did she wish she didn’t. After pegging up all the laundry she turned to walk back inside. Suddenly one of the fireflies touched her skin, scorching her. Looking closer, she realised that they weren’t fireflies, they were orbs of heat.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Annie picked up her pace and shut herself in the house, the neighbours were right, they were corpse candles! How? How, is it possible? It was just folklore, not the truth. Her heart beating in her ears she raced up the stairs to Benjamin’s room. Swinging open the door she realised with horror that the room was bare. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Running back down to the hall to her mother’s room, she noticed that their pictures were missing and that the lounge room was also furniture less. Swallowing the lump that was forming in her throat she threw open the door and cried, </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">mother! </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">But that room was also stripped bare.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">There were no traces of the Winchester family.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">She edged closer to the window which was frosted, she slowly wiped her sleeve and looked out. The lawn was a mess, the streets had changed, the moon was a deep honey yellow, casting elongated shadows.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Shuddering she backed up, away from the window. Where neighbours still next door? Even if they were she doubted that they’d let her stay with them. Why was the house empty? What had happened to Ben and mother?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“You were a good child,” a voice said from behind her and like a mouse she froze in her tracks. “What a pity you were marked by the candles.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Annie cautiously turned around and her breath caught, it was mother but also not at the same time. You see instead of fingers she had talons, long, sharp, blood-covered talons.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Come here deary,” it cooed.</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Lock on the Floor</title>
        <author>
            <name>RedEagle3</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/lock-on-the-floor/"/>
        <id>https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/lock-on-the-floor/</id>
            <category term="Short Stories"/>
            <category term="Halloween Vault 3D Entries 2020"/>

        <updated>2020-11-07T10:03:12+11:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/media/posts/11/163a706461a43151682877955735.png" alt="Horror Prompt: The Lock on The Floor" />
                    <p><strong>Before we start, I do not own The Evil Queen.</strong></p>
<p><strong>-RedEagle3</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">------------------------</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An alarm made James jump off the sofa and fall face-first into the hard, cold, wooden floor. He groaned in agony, it was Halloween, the one night he couldn’t sleep because of the chance of sighting an actual ghost or ghoul. He did it every Halloween and regretted it every Halloween because of the painful cycle of falling sleeping and falling onto the floor, most of the time, face-first.</span></p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/media/posts/11/163a706461a43151682877955735.png" alt="Horror Prompt: The Lock on The Floor" />
                <p><strong>Before we start, I do not own The Evil Queen.</strong></p>
<p><strong>-RedEagle3</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">------------------------</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An alarm made James jump off the sofa and fall face-first into the hard, cold, wooden floor. He groaned in agony, it was Halloween, the one night he couldn’t sleep because of the chance of sighting an actual ghost or ghoul. He did it every Halloween and regretted it every Halloween because of the painful cycle of falling sleeping and falling onto the floor, most of the time, face-first.</span></p>

<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rolling onto his back, he massaged his aching nose and picked up the glasses that had slid off his face while he was sleeping before tapping the alarm into silence. He stood up and stretched his sore back. After a fine assessment of all his multiple throbbing injuries, he went to the kitchen to grab an icepack and held it to his nose.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Two slow knocks sounded at his door.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Glancing at the kitchen clock, he wondered why someone would be trick or treating so late on Halloween.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Two more impatient knocks reverberated through the door.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Comming!” He called out to his unexpected visitor as he grabbed some candy and rushing to the door. As the door swung open, there was no living thing in sight accept a red-eyed rat which scuttled across the verandah at the sight of him.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Scratching his head he wondered what to do next. Was the rat secretly Pettigrew? If the rat was the only thing here, then who knocked? The only trace of a living thing other than that rat was the lock of hair on the floor of the veranda. It looked to be around a meter long, it was red at one end before turning into a night black. Maybe a trick or treater that had passed by before? That still didn’t explain the knock he’d heard just now. This seemed an awful lot like the plot of a horror movie.</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">on Halloween night, a boy called James is all alone in his house. He hears a knock at the door and wonders who would be trick or treating so late in the night. He opens the door and sees a strand of hair half hie height. What will happen next?</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Pushing away that thought, he went back to the sofa when a phantom chill passed through his body. Goosebumps slowly coved his arms and he grabbed a thick cloth in an attempt to warm up. It was almost like his bones were made of chilled copper, heavy as lead as if his essence itself was frozen. The chill crept through his body until his entire existence felt like his arms.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He could feel the intruder in his mind and wondered who it was.</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mortals, ever so ignorant.</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mortals?</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Most of them live, I can say the same for those who ate my apple. </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">It said and laughed a wicked laugh.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">An apple? The Evil Queen?</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">No one thinks I’m Halloween scary and for that, they will pay.</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Seriously, this was a bad fairy slash, old woman. There was nothing scary about her, she was just an ugly old hag. </span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Oh? </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">She said mockingly.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A slender woman with an icy beauty appeared in front of him. She had a poker face and a black veil but that was where the similarities between her and the Disney adaptation ended. She had a black fur coat over a dark shade of emerald green and golden embroidered jacket lehenga. A thick brass crown sat on her head and a raven sat on her shoulder, staring at him with its beady eyes.</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Let the fun begin.</span></i></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Lively Halloween</title>
        <author>
            <name>RedEagle3</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/lively-halloween/"/>
        <id>https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/lively-halloween/</id>
            <category term="Short Stories"/>
            <category term="Halloween Vault 3D Entries 2020"/>
            <category term="Editor&#x27;s pick"/>

        <updated>2020-11-05T18:56:38+11:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/media/posts/10/163a70062730ef76309128658978.png" alt="Profile Prompt: Lively Halloween" />
                    <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The sun sunk below the horizon taking the collage of oranges and pinks with it turning Strange Vale’s horizon into a deep purple freckled with sparkling stars that could’ve been mistaken for sugar. People’s verandas lined with carved pumpkins and fake cobwebs, some even had candles and what they thought were creepy</span> <span style="font-weight: 400;">orange lanterns. Unlike previous Halloweens, most children weren’t trick or treating because of all the quarantining happening. Kady’s family on the other hand thought that it was important to continue traditions. </span></p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://mkalpana.github.io/gh-pages/media/posts/10/163a70062730ef76309128658978.png" alt="Profile Prompt: Lively Halloween" />
                <p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The sun sunk below the horizon taking the collage of oranges and pinks with it turning Strange Vale’s horizon into a deep purple freckled with sparkling stars that could’ve been mistaken for sugar. People’s verandas lined with carved pumpkins and fake cobwebs, some even had candles and what they thought were creepy</span> <span style="font-weight: 400;">orange lanterns. Unlike previous Halloweens, most children weren’t trick or treating because of all the quarantining happening. Kady’s family on the other hand thought that it was important to continue traditions. </span></p>

<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So now she sat there on the sofa half-submerged in pillows, patiently waiting for her parents to leave with her brothers so she could take out her candy and enjoy some alone time, which seemed impossible lately.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“HEY! Joshua! That’s MY pumpkin!” Jake screamed. Jake was that young boy in everyone’s family that fussed over everything and if something didn’t go his way… he threw a tantrum.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Here,” Joshua sighed and gave Jake his pumpkin. Joshua was the cool-headed and responsible brother who managed to earn the respect of an adult. Living in a family with five meant that conversations almost always ended in screaming and hair-pulling. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Just when she thought she could have some peace and quiet her two brothers decided to enter her space.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Now now, don’t fight.” Their mother calmly said. She was every family’s wonderful mother who loved her kids beyond this universe. Their mother thought that it was a bad idea to go out during a pandemic but then again it was just once on a special occasion.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Who’s ready for some trick or treating!!!” Dad yelled from upstairs.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“We are, now come down honey.” Their dad descended the stars and Kady had trouble holding in her laughter as her father came into view.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“What do you think?”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“You look hilarious! People will definitely give us candy!” Jake yelled as he looked father up and down. He looked like he tried to dress as a scary vampire but for some reason, it looked more like a vampire monkey than the corpse that sucks blood from living people’s necks.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Well, enjoy having fun walking down deserted streets with a high chance of being eaten by monsters!” Kady enthusiastically wished her family. Earning an eye-roll form Joshua and a glare from her parents while Jake screamed for the second time in five minutes.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“What do you mean by getting eaten by monsters!”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Don’t listen to her, she’s just trying to make us you,” said Joshua rolling his eyes again.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“I’m not scared!” Jake yelled, now she strongly believed that for a nine-year-old Jake couldn’t open his mouth without screaming or yelling.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Well, there’s food in the fridge and some tea on the stove. Please be careful darling.” Their mother said before opening the door for Joshua and Jake. The three of them walking out the door and onto the pavement.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“You sure you don’t want to come along? You don’t have to dress up,” her father offered and she shook her head.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Nah, you four have fun!” She yelled at her family as her father jogged to catch up with the rest of their family.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Kady slowly closed the door and retrieved her box of candy which she was had been stashing since the beginning of September. Plopping down on the sofa she started to open a packet of m&amp;m’s popping one into her mouth. She grabbed the tv’s remote and turned the tv on to some random channel doing a Halloween special and slowly started to go through her month’s stockpile.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That was when it started to happen.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The lights started to flicker and the tv turned static. Slowly every room in the house was flooded in darkness. Kady sat there as still as a statue on the sofa, her fist full of candy corn midway her mouth.</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mistress, why have you summoned us. </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">A voice rang through the house, shaking its foundations and flakes of cement rained down like snow.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“I haven’t summoned anyone!” Kady yelled. “Come on! I know it’s you, Joshua and Jake! Why do you ruin my only alone time!”</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">I’m not a mortal mistress, </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">the voice threw back</span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">, if my assistance is not needed shall I leave?</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“That voice is so phoney.”</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">It is very real mistress, my patience is what’s phoney.</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Come out!”</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">As you wish…</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The floor near the basement creaked and Kady watched in horror as a hooded figure emerged from the corridor.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Who are you? What are you doing here? If you’re a burglar then know that I know how to throw a punch.” Kady bluffed, she was good at hacking not fighting. Maybe she could talk her way through this.</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Who am I? More like what am I. </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">The figure said as it lowed its hood making Kady want to scream. Half of its face was beautiful beyond belief, like Aphrodite’s face she could say but the other half was rotten to the skull, the skin just barely holding onto the bone.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Why are you here?”</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">You told your brothers that they could be eaten by monsters and it turns out you’re right.</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“What do you mean?!?”</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">I think you know Kady.</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Call it off, leave my family alone!”</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Are you sure? This could be the only chance of getting rid of them without being convicted.</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“You’re a twisted psychopath! I’ll repeat myself once more. Leave. My. Family. Alone.”</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">But are you-</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Do you want me to spell it for you? ‘Cuz I can.” Kady knew what she had to do, she had to act brave and like she had something up here sleeve if this </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">thing </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">didn’t corporate.</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Alright, mistress.</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“That’s not all. You also have to return everything to normal, like before you come here and leave and never return.” Kady ordered with her sternest face before her sight became black.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">P</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">I</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">T</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">C</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">H</span></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">B</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">L</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">C</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">K</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">She felt sluggish, her eyes felt glued together and she struggled to move her body.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Wake up Kady, we’re home.” An annoying voice stretched the speech. She sat up all of a sudden as the light got flipped on.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Looks like you slept off while watching tv!” Jake giggled.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Why is there candy all over the floor!” Her mother complained.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ahh, all the sweet noises of a family.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Are you all fine? Did you see any monsters?” Kady asked, genuinely worried for her family.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Nope, all in one piece, but my feet do feel like they’re ready to burst.” Her father voiced as he ascended the stairs.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That meant that it was all a dream, right?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Honey, whose robes are these?”</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
